Finding Aid for the A&M Records Records PASC-M.0269
UCLA Library Special Collections
A&M Records records
1910-2001
UCLA Library Special Collections
A & M Records (Firm)
PASC-M.0269
100 Linear Feet (197 boxes)
The collection consists of correspondence, production records, business records, photographs, music, artwork, posters, clippings, awards, ephemera, artifacts, sound recordings, and video recordings from just prior to the founding of A & M Records in 1962 to a few years after its sale to Polygram in 1989, while Jerry Moss and Herb Alpert were still affiliated with the label.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO AND AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audio and audiovisual materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Jerry Moss and Herb Alpert, March 2005.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9951521793606533
Biographical History
Founded in 1962 in Los Angeles, California by Jerry Moss and Herb Alpert, A&M Records became America's largest independent record company. Both men were born in 1935, Alpert in Los Angeles and Moss in New York. The two met in the early 1960s, when Alpert was writing and recording songs and Moss was an independent record promoter. Their social acquaintance quickly became a partnership when in 1962 the two formed Carnival Records, based in Alpert's garage. With contributions of $100 from each man, the company released the single "Tell It to the Birds." After discovering later that year that the Carnival name was already in use, Alpert and Moss created the company's new name from the initials of their last names.
A&M Records' first release, the single "The Lonely Bull" by Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass, came out in August 1962. It reached number six on the Billboard charts and sold some 700,000 copies. Other best-selling Tijuana Brass albums followed, including "Whipped Cream and Other Delights" and "What Now My Love." Led by the success of the Tijuana Brass, A&M revenue topped $50 million by 1968; by the end of the decade the band had sold some 45 million albums.
A&M's roster featured many of the top pop and rock acts from the 1960s, 1970s, and 1980s, including Bryan Adams, Burt Bacharach, Joan Baez, the Baja Marimba Band, the Captain and Tennille, the Carpenters, Cheech and Chong, Joe Cocker, Peter Frampton, Lani Hall, Janet Jackson, Joe Jackson, Sergio Mendes and Brasil '66, the Neville Brothers, Jeffrey Osborne, The Police, Squeeze, Cat Stevens, Sting, Styx, Supertramp, and the Tubes, among many others. A number of jazz composers and performers were also issued by the label, including Gato Barbieri, Quincy Jones and Paul Winter as well as some late recordings by Chet Baker and Stan Getz.
In 1989 Alpert and Moss sold A&M records to PolyGram Records.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of correspondence, production records, business records, photographs, music, artwork, posters, clippings, awards, ephemera, artifacts, Herb Alpert & The Tijuana Brass clothing, sound recordings, and video recordings.
Arrangement
The collection has been arranged into the following series:
Series 1: Correspondence, 1959-1992 Series 2: Production records, 1965-1988 Series 3: Business records, 1961-2001 Series 4: Photographs, 1960s-1980s Series 5: Music, 1917-1984 Series 6: Artwork, undated Series 7: Posters, 1971-1977 Series 8: Clippings, 1956-1989 Series 9: Awards, 1960-1989 Series 10: Ephemera and artifacts, 1957-1982 Series 11: Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass clothing, circa 1960s Series 12: Sound recordings, 1910-1999 Series 13: Video recordings, 1983-1991
Sound recording industry -- United States -- Archives.; Alpert, Herb; Moss, Jerry; A & M Records (Firm) -- Archives
- Correspondence, 1959-1992; Series 1.
  Scope and Content
  Herb Alpert's letters received primarily concern his events and performances with the Tijuana Brass; also Alpert's charitable activities, some fan letters, congratulatory telegrams, and thank yous. A few letters or telegrams are from other musicians. The bulk of Alpert's letters sent are copies of thank you letters, most with original letters received attached.
  Jerry Moss's correspondence mostly deals with A&M artists and the label's business activities, including with affiliates and divisions. Gil Friesen's correspondence, president of A&M from 1977-1990, concerns A&M's business, especially legal matters, and Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass television specials. Sal Monte's letters, road manager for Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass, detail travel and tour arrangements for the band.
  - Alpert, Herb--received, 1959-1989 (bulk 1960s), undated (Box 1, Box 2, Folder 1)
    Includes two letters from Chet Baker, November 12, 1968 (postmark date) and April 29, 1969 (both in box 1).
  - Alpert, Herb--sent, 1966-1990, undated (Box 2, Folder 2-5)
  - Moss, Jerry--received, 1965-1992, undated (Box 2, Folder 6-12, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Folder 1-3)
  - Moss, Jerry--sent, 1966-1990, undated (Box 5, Folder 4-10, Box 6, Folder 1-5)
  - Friesen, Gil--received, 1966-1989, undated (Box 6, Folder 6-9, Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - Friesen, Gil--sent, 1965-1969, undated (Box 7, Folder 3-5)
  - Monte, Sal--received, 1966-1975, undated (Box 7, Folder 6-7)
  - Monte, Sal--sent, 1966-1975, undated (Box 7, Folder 8-9)
  - Blair, Wynell, 1966-1968, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Cooper, Paul, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Fead, Bob, 1966-1969, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Graham, Don, 1966-1969 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Green, Derek, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Hubert, David, 1969-1975 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Li Puma, Tommy, 1966, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Ross, Carol--received, 1966-1970, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Ross, Carol--sent, 1966-1968, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - A & R Department, 1965-1966, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - General correspondence, 1964-1986, undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Includes letters to other staff, to A & M Records generally, or unknown recipients.
  - Staff memos, 1966-1990, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Herb Alpert framed correspondence, 1968 (Box 167)
    Framed telegrams and other items from Hubert Humphrey, Mace Neufeld, and the White House.
  - Herb Alpert birthday cards (Box 168)
- Production records, 1965-1990; Series 2.
  - Tours and concerts, 1965-1980s; Subseries 1.
    The bulk of this series consists of tour itineraries for Herb Alpert and the Tijuana Brass; also present are forms, receipts, equipment lists, and seating charts. In addition, there are two folders of pre-prepared stage banter for the group. A small amount of tour material is present for the Baja Marimba Band, Sergio Mendes and Brasil '66, and a few other A&M artists.
    Material is most likely from the files of Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass's Road Manager Sal Monte or Assistant Road Manager Bill Earl. See also Sal Monte's correspondence in box 7 for additional tour-related material.
    - Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass, 1965-1970s, undated (Box 8, Folder 11-12, Box 9, Folder 1-5)
    - Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass: stage banter, undated (Box 9, Folder 6-7)
    - Herb Alpert: Public relations tour and other travel/publicity (Bill Earl file), 1980s (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Baja Marimba Band / Sergio Mendes & Brasil '66, 1966-1969, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Other groups / unknown, 1968-1985, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Notes and ephemera, 1969, undated (Box 10, Folder 2-3)
  - Television, 1967-1990; Subseries 2.
    Contains primarily scripts, shooting schedules, and agreements for various Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass television specials. For photographs relating to the group's television specials and appearances see Series 4.
    - Singer Presents Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Hollywood Palace, 1967, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - The Beat of the Brass, 1967-1969, undated (Box 10, Folder 6-9, Box 11, Folder 1-2)
    - The Brass Are Comin', 1969 (Box 11, Folder 3-6)
    - Other television, 1966-1969, 1990, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Other productions, 1987-1988, undated; Subseries 3. (Box 11, Folder 8-9)
    Includes an outline and lyrics for the concept album White Mansions and a script for the musical Pandemonium.
- Business records, 1961-2001; Series 3.
  - Jerry Moss, 1978-1981, 1990, undated; Subseries 1. (Box 12, Folder 1-3, Box 17)
    Includes Moss's copies of the final report of sale of A&M assets to affiliates of PolyGram N.V. (1990) (box 17), as well as appointment books and notes (box 12).
  - Divisions and affiliates, 1978-1990; Subseries 2.
    Includes operational reports, agreements, negotiations, and some financial and distribution reports.
    - A&M Europe, 1978-1990 (Box 12, Folder 4-7, Box 13, Folder 1)
    - RCA/BMG, 1979-1988 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Windham Hill, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Festival Records, 1974-1987 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Other, 1990, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Music publishing, 1965-1990; Subseries 3.
    Rondor Music records are primarily management accounts. The bulk of Almo/Irving material is catalogs.
    Rondor Music, Almo Music Corp, and Irving Music Inc. were all music publishing groups established by Herb Alpert and Jerry Moss in 1962. Almo Music Corp. was formally incorporated on October 5, 1962. Irving Music. Inc. was brought into the Alpert and Moss partnership by Moss.
    - Rondor Music, 1987-1990, undated (Box 13, Folder 6-7)
    - Almo Music Corp. / Irving Music Inc., 1965, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Contracts and agreements, 1962-1987; Subseries 4. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Primarily includes various contracts and agreements for appearances and music publishing, mostly for Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass. There are no recording contracts for A&M artists present.
  - Personnel, 1966-1990, undated; Subseries 5. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Includes A&M staff bios and lists, some benefits information, and programs relating to staff meetings and events.
  - Financial, 1961-1988, undated; Subseries 6. (Box 14, Folder 2-3)
    Includes several royalty statements for Herb Alpert (1961-1970), and a small amount of various invoices, rate schedules, earnings projections, salary information, and a stock report (1988). Also included is an early A&M checkbook with stubs from 1962-1963 and a ledger from 1957, possibly for Alpert's songwriting venture for Keen Records.
  - Marketing and sales, 1962-1990; Subseries 7.
    Some artist biographies and press releases / kits contain publicity photos. Artists include Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass, Sergio Mendes & Brasil '66, Baja Marimba Band, the Carpenters, Humble Pie, Carole King, Joan Baez, and others.
    - Artist rosters and bios (Box 14, Folder 4-5)
    - Press releases and kits / promotions, 1966-1983, undated (Box 14, Folder 6-7)
    - Sales and charts, 1966-1977 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
    - Reports, 1970, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Herb Alpert - Fandango research report, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Herb Alpert - Press clippings report, circa 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 5-6)
    - Other, 1962-1969, circa 1980 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Discographies and awards, 1986-2001; Subseries 8. (Box 16, Folder 1-4, Box 17)
  - Reports: Not related to A&M, 1970-1989; Subseries 9. (Box 16, Folder 5-6)
    This subseries contains various reports for the National Association of Recording Merchandisers, Shelter Records, the Alpert Family Foundation, the Los Angeles Olympic Organizing Committee, and promotional reports and catalogs of non-A&M artists.
  - Programs, notes, and ephemera, 1966-1968, 1986, undated; Subseries 10. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Includes programs for tribute events for Herb Alpert and Jerry Moss.
- Photographs, 1960s-1980s; Series 4.
  - Photographs of Herb Alpert and the Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass, 1960s-1970s; Subseries 1.
    - Promotional photographs and portraits (Box 18, Folder 1-2, Box 21, Folder 1-3)
      Includes some autographed photographs.
    - Casual snapshots (Box 18, Folder 3-6, Box 21, Folder 4, Box 168, Folder 1)
      Images primarily depict Alpert with other entertainment or public figures, including Jerry Lewis, Queen Elizabeth, Lyndon Johnson, Sergio Mendes, Eddie Fisher, and Steve Allen. Oversize photographs in box 21 also include Harry Belafonte and Dizzy Gillespie. Also present are snapshots of Alpert receiving a star on the Walk of Fame (box 18), as well as Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass's trip to Tijuana (box 18, folder 6).
    - Performances (Box 18, Folder 7-8, Box 21, Folder 5-7)
      Photographs of various performances, plus numerous snapshots of the group on tour. Includes a color photograph of a performance at the White House, 1967 (box 21, folder 6).
    - Television specials (Box 18, Folder 9, Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Promotional events (Box 18, Folder 10)
      Includes many photographs of Whipped Cream & Other Delights album cover recreations.
    - Childhood and family (Box 22, Folder 2, Box 168, Folder 1)
      Photographs of Alpert's childhood home, and high school. (Photograph of Alpert's mother with Jerry Moss's mother: box 168, folder 1.)
    - Contact sheets (Box 19, Folder 1, Box 22, Folder 3, Box 168, Folder 2)
    - Negatives (Box 19, Folder 2-4)
  - Photographs of other A&M artists, 1960s-1980s; Subseries 2.
    Includes photographs of the Baja Marimba Band, Sergio Mendes & Brasil '66, Lani Hall (solo and with Brasil '66), Chuck Mangione, Joan Armatrading, Quincy Jones, Chris Montez, Atlantic Starr, Gino Vanelli, Tim Curry, Sister Janet Mead, Supertramp, Billy Preston, Pablo Cruz, Claudine Longet, the Dickies, and others. Oversize photographs include Rita Coolidge and Burt Bacharach (box 22, folder 5).
    - Baja Marimba Band (Box 19, Folder 5, Box 22, Folder 4)
      Includes color photograph of the group's White House performance, 1966; autographed by President Lyndon Johnson and Lady Bird Johnson (box 22, folder 4).
    - Sergio Mendes & Brasil '66 / Lani Hall (Box 19, Folder 6, Box 22, Folder 4)
      Includes numerous black and white snapshots of a recording session of the band, as well as of Lanu Hall solo (box 22).
    - Others (Box 19, Folder 7-8, Box 22, Folder 5-6)
    - Contact sheets (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Negatives - Frank Gorshin, 1960s (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Personnel and workplace photographs, 1960s-1970s; Subseries 3. (Box 19, Folder 11, Box 20, Folder 1-2, Box 22, Folder 7, Box 23, Box 168, Folder 3)
    Photographs of Jerry Moss, Herb Alpert, Gil Friesen, Harold Childs, and other A&M executives and staff, some of which include A&M artists including Peter Frampton and Styx. box 168, folder 3; the Carpenters, the Police, Quincy Jones, George Harrison box 20, folder 1. Also present are shots of the A&M lot and offices on La Brea Avenue in Hollywood and of the A&M recording studio. Includes some contact sheets and negatives.
    Photograph of Jerry Moss's and Herb Alpert's mothers is located in Subseries 1 (box 168, folder 1).
    Includes an oversize mounted photo of Alpert, Moss, and Friesen (box 23).
  - Unidentified photographs, Subseries 4. (Box 20, Folder 3, Box 22, Folder 8, Box 168, Folder 4 and 32)
- Music, 1917-1984; Series 5.
  - Amanhecer, copy of lead sheet (Box 180, Folder 16)
  - Amar Amargo, horn 1 & 2: tpt 1,2,3,4: tbn1,2,3; Ozalid prints of parts (Box 180, Folder 17)
  - America, piano; manuscript lead sheet (Box 180, Folder 18)
  - And the angels sing, Vln, Gtr, Bass, Harps, Dms; manuscript parts and ozalid prints of parts (Box 180, Folder 19)
  - And there's nothing you can do, lead sheet; Ozalid prints (Box 180, Folder 20)
  - And we were strangers, copy of lead sheet (Box 180, Folder 21)
  - And when you've gone, manuscript lead sheet (Box 180, Folder 22)
  - Angelito, marimba and vibes; manuscript parts and ozalid prints of parts (Box 180, Folder 23)
  - Anna, manuscript lead sheet and copies (Box 180, Folder 24)
  - Anniversary song, rhythm; copy (Box 180, Folder 25)
  - Anything Love Can Buy (Box 180, Folder 26)
  - Apple Jade And Silver Beads, cl;tpt;sax;tbn;vln;vla;vcl;mar;gtr;pno;dm; holograph transparancies and ozalid prints of parts (Box 76, Folder 1)
    General note
    Lyrics also by Charles M. Jones.
  - As long as you love me, Ozalid prints of parts (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Atelago, manuscript parts (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Attitude, photocopy of lead sheet (Box 76, Folder 4)
    Also written by Bill Labounty.
  - Avenues And Alleyways, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    Photocopy.
  - B.S. #1, manuscript parts (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - I told you so (back to Cuernavaca), 1963 October; Ozalid prints of parts (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Bajanova, 1967; Ozalid prints of parts (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Banquet, Ozalid prints of parts (Box 76, Folder 10)
    Lani Hall
  - Beacon Hill Theme, 1975; Ozalid prints of parts (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - A Beautiful Friend, trumpet, trombone, rhythm; manuscript parts and photocopy (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - [Untitled], 1968 October; manuscript parts (Box 76, Folder 13)
    Recorded Baja
  - Because of you, 1940; manuscript parts and published music (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Believe in me, 1970; photocopy of lead sheet (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Bell that couldn't jingle, the, choir, violins, violas, celli; holograph transparencies and ozalid prints of parts (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Bells, 1970; Ozalid prints of parts (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Belz mein shtetele belz (my hometown belz), photocopy of lead sheet (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Better Use Your Head, photocopy of lead sheet (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Beyond the Surf (Box 76, Folder 30)
  - Big, big blues, Ozalid prints of parts (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - The Biggest Man In Town, 1964; holograph transparencies (Box 76, Folder 23)
    Also written by: Frank D'Amico.
  - Bittersweet Samba, tpt;tbn;rhy; Ozalid prints of parts (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - Black forest, tpt;tbn;rhy; photocopy of parts and ozalid copies of parts (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - Blipidy-Blap(Shoutin Blues) (Box 76, Folder 29)
  - Blue bird, photocopy of lead sheet (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - Bluebird, 1975; photocopy of lead sheet (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - Blue summer rain, Ozalid prints of parts (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - Blue Sunday, tpt., tbn., rhy.; manuscript parts and photocopies (of rhythm part) (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Bo Bo, tpt., tbn., rhy.; manuscript parts and photocopies (of rhythm part) (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Bolz, tbn., gtr., bass, dms.; manuscript trombone part and lead sheet, photocopies of lead sheet (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Bongo (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Boop, 1961; Ozalid prints of part (unspecified instrumentation) (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Bossa Bossa, 1964; Ozalid prints of part (unspecified instrumentation) (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Boy You Better Think It Over, 1984; photocopied part (unspecified instrumentation) (Box 77, Folder 7)
    Also written by: Aaron Zigman.
  - The brass are comin', tpt., tbn., rhy.; manuscript parts and photocopies (of rhythm part) (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Brazilia, Tijuana Brass (tpt., tbn., rhy.); manuscript score, manuscript parts, Ozalid prints of score, photocopies of parts (Box 77, Folder 10)
    TJB 22
  - Bud's-a-nova, Ozalid print of lead sheet (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Bull, tbn.; manuscript part (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Foxhunt, photocopied lead sheet (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Cabaret, 1966; trumpet, trombone, rhythm; Ozalid prints of rhy. part and piano reduction, photocopies of tpt., tbn., and rhy. part, published piano reduction (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - California nights, tpt.; manuscript tpt. part and lead sheet, photocopies (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - California poppy, tpt., tbn., 2 vcl., rhy.; manuscript lead sheet and parts, (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Can you read my mind, synth.; manuscript part (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Canada, hrn., rhy.; manuscript parts and photocopies (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Canato do Mar-ino, Ozalid print of lead sheet (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Carmen, com; tpt; picc; perc; gtr; bass; dms; manuscript parts and ozalid prints of parts (Box 78, Folder 1)
    instrumentation (continued): conductor; Herb+orch.
  - Carmine, vln; vcl; Ozalind prints of parts (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Casino Royale, rhy; herb; 2 tpt; pno; tbn; bass; perc; mar; manuscript parts and ozalid prints of parts (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Catch a falling star, tpt; Ozalind prints of parts (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Cat's, tpt; rhy; manuscript parts (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - 'Cause I'm so in love with you, Ozalind prints of parts (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Charge, pno; gtr; organ; rhy; manuscript parts and ozalid prints of parts (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Charlie (From the ciuerama production "the statue"), Ozalid prints of parts (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Chase the cloud away, photocopied parts (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - The charmer, tpt; rhy; manuscript parts and ozalid prints of parts (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Chicken walk, tbn; gtr; pno; dms; manuscript parts and ozalid prints of parts (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Chili con go go, manuscript parts (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Chris, manuscript parts and ozalid prints of parts (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - A Christmas Camel, photocopied parts (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - A Christmas Letter, Ozalind prints of parts (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Xmas song, choir; chords; Ozalind prints of parts (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Cinco de mayo, manuscript parts and ozalid prints of parts (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Clarence, 1975; photocopy of lead sheet (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Claudine, photocopy of lead sheet (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Close to you, Ozalid prints of parts (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Colin da, Ozalid prints of parts (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Come down in time, photocopy of lead sheet (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Come on back where you belong - (1975 version), 1973; manuscript parts (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Come Touch the Sun, Ozalid prints of parts (Box 79, Folder 8)
    From the 20th century fox picture "Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid."
  - Come in the back door, manuscript parts (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Coney island, 1974; photocopy of lead sheet (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - The Continental, rhy;pno;chor; manuscript parts, photocopy of published music, photocopy of parts and ozalid copies of parts (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - The Continental American, 1974; photocopy of lead sheet (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Conquistador, 1967; photocopy of lead sheet (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Corrida de jangada, photocopy of lead sheet (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Country lake, tpt;tbn;rhy; Manuscript parts and photocopies of parts (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Cowboys and indians, tpt;tbn;vln;vla;rhy; Manuscript parts and photocopies of parts (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Cow hand, manuscript parts and photocopies of parts (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Crazy arms, chor;strg;acc;vib;gtr; manuscript parts and ozalid prints of parts (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Crea mi amor, tpt;tbn;rhy; manuscript parts and photocopies of parts (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Cross road, manuscript parts (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Cuando, manuscript parts and ozalid prints of parts (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Daddy, tbn;vln;vla;gtr;bass;dms; Ozalid prints of parts and photocopies of parts (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Daisy, i'm so glad that it rained, 1969; photocopy of lead sheet (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Daughter of Peggy O'Neil, the, photocopy of published music (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - Day train, rhy; holograph transparancies and ozalid copies of parts (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - Day of sand, vibes; manuscript parts and photocopies of parts (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - Deep is the sea, lead sheet (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Delilah, Tpt., Rhy.; manuscript and photocopy parts (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Diablo's dance, lead sheet manuscript (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Dida, Tpt., Tbn., Rhy.; music manuscripts and photocopy (Box 80, Folder 4)
    84